Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The Delaware QSOS
    - Pat Henry oral history interview conducted by Lori Miller, 2003-03-03 (Interview-id DE19958-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR288
    - Dianne Deming oral history interview conducted by Kelli Lucas, 2003-03-03 (Interview-id DE19958-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR289; AFC 2007/009: SR290
    - Eleanor Goldsmith oral history interview conducted by Heather Gibson, 2003-03-03 (Interview-id DE19958-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, draft and final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR291
    - Nancy King Hovis oral history interview conducted by Nikki Green, 2002-03-03 (Interview-id DE19958-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, draft and final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR292
    - Maud Hastings oral history interview conducted by Lori Miller, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR293
    - Diana Ziegler oral history interview conducted by Megan Dwyre, 2003-10-10 (Interview-id DE19963-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR294; AFC 2007/009: SR295
    - Ellie Guest oral history interview conducted by Megan Dwyre, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR296; AFC 2007/009: SR297
    - Judy Manlove oral history interview conducted by Rachel Grove, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, final transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR297; AFC 2007/009: SR298
    - M.L. Kaczka oral history interview conducted by Rachel Grove, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR299
    - Shirley Cherneski oral history interview conducted by Lori Miller, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR300
    - Marlene Kosnac oral history interview conducted by Lori Miller, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR301; AFC 2007/009: SR302
    - Roberta Korona oral history interview conducted by Megan Dwyre, 2003-10-19 (Interview-id DE19963-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR303
    - Mimi Sparks oral history interview, 2002-04-20 (Interview-id DE20)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR275
    - Amy Tetlow Smith oral history interview conducted by Julie Henderson, 2002-08-14 (Interview-id UDel-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, sign for photograph
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR441
    - Nancy Smith oral history interview conducted by David Smith, 2002-08-20 (Interview-id UDel-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, Zip drive label, 5 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_Udel_002_01.doc; afc2007009_Udel_002_02-06.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR442
    - Peg Reagle oral history interview conducted by Amy Tetlow Smith, 2003-06-10 (Interview-id UDel-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR443
    - Sandy Bryant oral history interview conducted by Amy Tetlow Smith, 2003-07-29 (Interview-id UDel-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR444
    - Antha Jones oral history interview conducted by Amy Tetlow Smith, 2003-08-26 (Interview-id UDel-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR445
    - Arlene Favreau-Pysher oral history interview conducted by Amy Tetlow Smith, 2004-01-09 (Interview-id UDel-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR446
    - Dorothy Orr oral history interview conducted by Amy Tetlow Smith, 2004-02-10 (Interview-id UDel-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR447
  - The Denmark QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Denmark.
    - Sharon Benton oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, April 26-May 4, 2007 (Interview-id DNK-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_DNK_001_03.doc; afc2007009_DNK_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_DNK_001_02.jpg
  - The Elkhorn City, Kentucky QSOS
    Ronda Coleman, QSOS volunteer, conducted interviews with quiltmakers in her community. Many of these quiltmakers participate in a class given by the Elkhorn City Public Library.
    - Sue Ramey oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-01-17 (Interview-id KY41522-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_001_01.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_001_04.jpg
    - Eloise Ratliff oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-01-31 (Interview-id KY41522-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital documents, 4 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_002_01.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_002_07.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_002_03-06.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_002_02.wma
    - Roberta Bartley oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-02-07 (Interview-id KY41522-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_003_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_003_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_003_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_003_01.wma
    - Marie Coleman oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-02-21 (Interview-id KY41522-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital documents, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_004_01.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_004_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_004_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_004_03.jpg
    - Sue Hackney oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-02-21 (Interview-id KY41522-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_005_03.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_005_04.wma
    - Jessie Taylor oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-02-18 (Interview-id KY41522-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_006_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_006_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_006_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_006_05.wma
    - Ruby Hawkins oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-06 (Interview-id KY41522-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_007_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_007_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_007_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_007_01.wma
    - Dicie Sloan oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-06 (Interview-id KY41522-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_008_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_008_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_008_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_008_01.wma
    - Paulette Runyon oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-13 (Interview-id KY41522-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_009_05.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_009_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_009_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_009_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_009_04.wma
    - Kathy Stewart oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-13 (Interview-id KY41522-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_010_05.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_010_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_010_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_010_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_010_04.wma
    - Clinton Belcher oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-20 (Interview-id KY41522-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_KY41522_011_02.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_011_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_011_03.wma
    - Pamela Prater oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-20 (Interview-id KY41522-012)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_012_03.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_012_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_012_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_012_04.wma
    - Ivel Hunt oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-03-20 (Interview-id KY41522-013)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–3 images; 2 digital documents, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_013_04.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_013_05.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_013_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_013_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_013_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_013_06.wma
    - Colene Adkins oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-04-03 (Interview-id KY41522-014)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_014_03.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_014_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_014_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_014_04.wma
    - Annette Kendrick oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-04-17 (Interview-id KY41522-015)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_015_03.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_015_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_015_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_015_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_015_04.wma
    - Charlene Hopkins oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-04-22 (Interview-id KY41522-016)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_016_03.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_016_01.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_016_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_016_04.wma
    - Myrtle Bartley oral history interview conducted by Ronda Coleman, 2008-10-09 (Interview-id KY41522-017)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_KY41522_017_05.doc; afc2007009_KY41522_017_03.jpg; afc2007009_KY41522_017_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY41522_017_02.wma
  - The Florida QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Florida.
    - Sibyl Tarbell oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2007-04-22 (Interview-id FL33904-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript draft, letter from AFAQ
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR531; AFC 2007/009: SR532
    - Sheilana Massey oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2007-04-22 (Interview-id FL33922-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript draft, letter from AFAQ
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR533
    - Isis Marshall oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2006-04-09 (Interview-id FL33956-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR304
    - Joyce Moon oral history interview conducted by Joanne Gasperik, 2006-04-17 (Interview-id FL33956-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR305
  - The Georgia QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Georgia.
    - Jessie McCoy oral history interview conducted by Jodie Davis, 2010-10-14 (Interview-id GA30188-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA30188_001_01.doc; afc2007009_GA30188_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_GA30188_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_GA30188_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_GA30188_001_05.wav
    - Regina Carter oral history interview, 2010-10-15 (Interview-id GA30188-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA30188_002_01.doc; afc2007009_GA30188_002_03.jpg; afc2007009_GA30188_002_04.jpg; afc2007009_GA30188_002_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_GA30188_002_02.wav
    - Laura Wasilowski oral history interview conducted by Jodie Davis, 2010-10-16 (Interview-id GA30188-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_GA30188_003_01.docx; afc2007009_GA30188_003_02.jpg; afc2007009_GA30188_003_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_GA30188_003_04.wav
    - Abigail Kokai oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-11-25 (Interview-id GA31401-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA31401_001_06.doc; afc2007009_GA31401_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_GA31401_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_GA31401_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_GA31401_001_01.wav
  - The Germany QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Germany.
    - Petra Voegtle oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, April 21-25, 2007 (Interview-id DEU-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, email from Voegtle to Musgrave, 16 pages, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_DEU_001_03.doc; afc2007009_DEU_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_DEU_001_02.jpg
    - Margret Zalfen oral history interview conducted by Tomme Fent, 2008-09-13 (Interview-id DEU-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 3 digital documents, 4 digital images; afc2007009_DEU_002_03.doc; afc2007009_DEU_002_01.pdf; afc2007009_DEU_002_04.pdf; afc2007009_DEU_002_05-08.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_DEU_002_02.wav
    - Irene Kahmann oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-11-21 (Interview-id DEU-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_DEU_003_05.doc; afc2007009_DEU_003_02.jpg; afc2007009_DEU_003_03.jpg; afc2007009_DEU_003_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_DEU_003_01.wav
  - The Healing Quilts in Medicine QSOS
    Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, conducted interviews with the quiltmakers involved in making art quilts for the oncology waiting areas of Walter Reed Army Medical Center. The theme of the quilts was the plants and animals used to make the medicine in chemotherapies. The interviews were made possible by a grant from Lisa Ellis.
    - Judy Busby oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-24 (Interview-id VA22003-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, Artist’s statement, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_001_04.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_VA22003_001_05.wav; afc2007009_VA22003_001_06.wav
    - Cyndi Zacheis Souder oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-26 (Interview-id VA22003-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_002_06.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_002_02.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_VA22003_002_04.wav
    - Sandi Goldman oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-31 (Interview-id VA22003-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_003_07.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_003_05.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_003_06.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_VA22003_003_02.wav; afc2007009_VA22003_003_01.wav
    - Donna Marcinkowski DeSoto oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-05-13 (Interview-id VA22003-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_004_03.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_004_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_004_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_VA22003_004_04.wav
    - Carole Nicholas oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-05-18 (Interview-id VA22003-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_005_07.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 4 digital recordings; afc2007009_VA22003_005_03-06.wav
    - Annabel Ebersole oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-05-27 (Interview-id VA22003-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout, 1 4x6 color print-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_006_05.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_006_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_VA22003_006_02.wav
    - Norma Colman oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-06-12 (Interview-id VA22003-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_007_08.doc; afc2007009_VA22003_007_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_007_02.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_007_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_VA22003_007_06.wav; afc2007009_VA22003_007_04.wav
    - Elizabeth Byrom oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-02 (Interview-id VA22003-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital images; afc2007009_VA22003_008_01.jpg; afc2007009_VA22003_008_02.jpg
  - The Idaho QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Idaho.
    - Crane Johnson oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-08-04 (Interview-id ID83616-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ID83616_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ID83616_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ID83616_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ID83616_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_ID83616_001_05.wav
  - The Illinois QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Illinois.
    - Robbi Eklow oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, July 10-12, 2007 (Interview-id IL60030-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_IL60030_001_01.doc; afc2007009_IL60030_001_02.jpg
    - Barbara Schneider oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-11-04 (Interview-id IL60098-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_IL60098_001_07.doc; afc2007009_IL60098_001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_IL60098_001_05.wav
    - Alice Sommerville oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2003-04-16 (Interview-id IL60137-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR340; AFC 2007/009: SR341
    - Diane Fisher oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2004-06-02 (Interview-id IL60137-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR342
    - Barbara Wester oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-20 (Interview-id IL60540-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IL60540_001_06.doc; afc2007009_IL60540_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IL60540_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_IL60540_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_IL60540_001_04.wav
    - Sylvain Bergeron oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-03-01 (Interview-id IL60543-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Description of quilt, transcript, 3 color printouts (from digital images), 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_IL60543_001_02.doc; afc2007009_IL60543_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IL60543_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_IL60543_001_04.wav
    - Valli Schiller oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-12-19 (Interview-id IL60564-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 color printouts (from digital images), 4 b/w color printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_IL60564_001_05.doc; afc2007009_IL60564_001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR566
    - Merry Silber oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2002-08-23 (Interview-id IL60601-01)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 3x5 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR343
    - Julie Silber oral history interview conducted by Amy Henderson, 2002-08-23 (Interview-id IL60601-02)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 3x5 color print
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR344; AFC 2007/009: SR345
    - Linda Gass oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-11-12 (Interview-id IL60610-001)